You didn't die?
I'm still alive.
Thanks to you.
♪ Time flies like a dream ♪
♪ I remember every moonlight ♪
Two grown men,
acting like children.
Mentor.
I just wanted to see if he was okay.
I'm fully recovered.
I'm fine now.
♪ The memories overlap like a dream ♪
The Zhang family's miraculous medicine
is really extraordinary.
♪ What is lost and found again
runs deeper than farewell ♪
Are you really fine now?
You should worry about yourself.
[Archives: The Nanyang Mystery]
[Episode 16]
The headquarters is still the best.
If I got these injuries in Nanyang,
I'd be dead by now.
It hurts. Be gentle.
Shrimpie.
The three of us
will live a good life here from now on.
You should thank me and Zhang Haixia
for changing your dressings.
That's why you recovered so quickly.
You got like this just from doing a job.
So useless.
I'm not entirely useless, am I?
Didn't I bring him back?
What about his legs?
Didn't Mentor say
that this antidote cures all diseases?
That means there's still a chance
for my legs to recover.
Really?
Are you kidding?
Really.
The Zhang family's miraculous medicine
is absolutely effective.
He has an incomplete spinal injury,
meaning his spinal cord is damaged,
but some neural pathways remain.
In this situation,
the patient might retain some sensation
and motor function.
And Zhang Hailou,
thanks to your dedication
over the past three years,
caring for his legs
and helping him
with rehabilitation exercises,
his muscles
haven't atrophied too severely.
The medicine from downstairs
in the Archives
has already started to take effect on him.
He has a chance to stand up again.
Did you bump your head?
No.
As soon as I came back and saw...
that Shrimpie is still alive,
and his legs can recover,
it just feels a bit too good
to be true.
Stop laughing.
Isn't this the Zhang family's old mansion?
You're the daughter
of the Dong family now.
Why did you move back to the old mansion?
The Dong family was bombed.
It's being rebuilt.
So I bought this place back
in the name of the Dong family.
It feels good
to spend other people's money.
You didn't expect this, did you?
After all these years,
we can still come back here.
From now on, we'll be just like before,
living here together.
How wonderful would it be.
Finally, we're all back.
Let's go look around.
Let's go.
Shrimpie.
Mentor even restored this place?
Mentor!
What is this?
I'm done playing.
Mentor, we're done playing!
Mentor, come out.
We're done playing.
Mentor!
You're tricking me again!
You two idiots!
You fell into such a simple trap!
Stay hungry today.
I can't hold on anymore! Help!
Mentor!
I can't hold on, Mentor!
Zhang Hailou.
You're a member of the Zhang family now.
You need to act like a Zhang.
Starting tomorrow,
you will undergo
the Zhang family's training.
What training?
This.
When you can pull this brick out,
you'll have completed your first lesson.
Take your time.
Are you kidding me?
Cut the crap.
Zhang Haixia also needs to continue
his rehabilitation.
You two do your own things.
Don't bother each other.
We don't have many days to waste.
There are still many things
to handle in the Archives.
Are you even human?
Shouldn't we be reminiscing
about the past,
recalling the good times,
and feeling the moment
at a time like this?
Reminiscing about the past?
Alright.
Then tell me about all the
good deeds you did in Nanyang one by one.
Let's start...
with the Evil God Case.
Th-That's a long story.
Why don't you go first?
Mentor.
Well, it's been 10 years.
It's...
It's all in the past.
Mentor, you...
How come you haven't aged at all?
Share your skincare
secrets with me, will you?
Tell me.
I suddenly remembered
something very important.
Come with me.
[iKiwi Film Company]
The important thing you mentioned
was just coming out to eat?
Me being hungry
is the most important thing in the world.
Why not eat at home?
It's Mid-Autumn Festival today.
Just listen to Mentor.
[Jufang Restaurant]
Miss, gentlemen, your Siguo Soup,
pancakes,
sandworm jelly...
Shrimpie,
have a sausage first.
Stir-fried dried tofu,
pearl meatballs,
fresh fish dumplings,
lovebirds fish rolls,
and American crispy puffs.
All the dishes are here.
Enjoy your meal.
Are you crying?
Have you no conscience?
You didn't even cry for me,
but now you're crying for some food?
You don't understand.
I've been craving this for 10 years.
Excuse me.
Please bring us another round
of all these dishes later.
Okay.
Come on, try this.
Mentor,
can't the cooks in the Dong family
make these dishes?
Of course it's because
there's something good here.
Excuse me.
Coming!
Miss.
I heard you have the best
Green Spring wine in Xiacheng.
I can tell you know your stuff.
Green Spring
is our signature.
Many guests come here especially for it.
What vintage do you want?
The older, the better.
Then it depends on your luck today.
Look, this jar of
20-year-old wine
[Green Spring]
is our best.
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Whoever wins the dice game
and takes the title of "Top Scholar"
gets this 20-year-old wine.
Four red fours! Top Scholar!
[Four red fours] [Five of a kind with an ace]
[Top Scholar with two aces] [Five kings] [Six fours]
Top Scholar!
You have good luck, Miss.
My turn!
Five of a kind with an ace!
Bigger than four red fours!
[Four red fours] [Five of a kind with an ace]
[Top Scholar with two aces] [Five kings] [Six fours]
Five fours.
Five kings!
The biggest Top Scholar so far!
The three of you
all made Top Scholar in a row.
We will definitely
have good luck next year!
However,
[Green Spring]
we only have one jar of Green Spring.
You three will have to share it.
It's fine. We are together.
Hold on.
Since there's only one jar,
whoever gets the highest roll wins it.
You two brats.
When I started gambling,
your parents were still wearing diapers.
Put it down.
You old woman.
We didn't spend all these years out there
-making a living for nothing!
-What did you call me?
Since there are three of us...
You...
Let's play big.
Whoever rolls the lowest
pays for everyone!
-Great!
-Really?
Bravo!
Really?
Great!
Awesome!
This big?
Do you have a plan?
You go first.
I learned all my cheating tricks
from Mentor.
What should we do?
Are you stupid?
I also learned them from her.
Aren't you full of tricks?
Think of something.
Six fours!
The biggest Top Scholar so far!
Awesome!
Do you have money on you?
No.
What should we do?
We're on the same team.
He'll pay if we lose.
You do it.
Another one!
Again?
Again!
Still winning?
Awesome. Awesome.
A win!
A win again!
A win! A win!
A win!
Bravo!
Top Scholar with two aces!
Shrimpie, we won!
We won!
Shrimpie!
Congratulations, Top Scholars.
Today is the Mid-Autumn Festival.
Here is a photographer.
He can take a picture of you
to record this wonderful moment.
Mentor,
I want to take it standing up.
Shrimpie, let me help you.
Come on, bottoms up.
It's rare to have good wine.
I want some spicy fish.
Haixia, make it for me tomorrow.
Mentor.
Spicy fish—if he makes it tomorrow,
you won't get to eat it.
You'll have to wait a few days.
Talking back again!
You've been talking back to me
since childhood!
I mean... let's...
Let's talk business.
The Archives.
The Residence was attacked,
the Ship King was killed,
and the Archives were almost made public.
There's been such a huge disturbance
in Xiacheng.
I need time to deal with the aftermath.
I need to go out for a few days.
You two can take the opportunity
to rest.
Rest? Does something this good
really exist?
Let's go fishing tomorrow.
We haven't fished in a long time.
And when Mentor comes back,
we can have spicy fish.
Didn't you use to hate me fishing
the most?
Every time we came out fishing,
you said...
you said I cheated.
This time,
you prepare good bait for me,
and I'll let you get
a three-fish head start. Okay?
Why? Why?
[iKiwi Film Company]
Shrimpie.
So nice.
Look at that!
Look!
It started!
Over there!
[iKiwi Film Company]
♪ The past fades into traces on the page ♪
♪ A silent breeze
brushes past that lingering warmth ♪
[iKiwi Film Company]
♪ In this fleeting world,
I long for a moment of vivid life ♪
So beautiful.
♪ I may have a chance to open a door ♪
♪ Where love and wish
meet in a fleeting moment ♪
♪ There's no need to ask questions
in the maze ♪
Shrimpie,
look at the green one.
♪ The world's bustle ♪
♪ Can briefly warm
those under a shared roof ♪
[iKiwi Film Company]
♪ And the story has come to an end ♪
[Xiacheng News]
[Crossword Puzzle]
Come on.
Try to move.
Push.
Yes.
Good.
Good!
Take a rest.
Let's stop here for today.
Doctor.
How much longer will it take
before I can try to walk?
You're making fast progress.
Miss Dong told me
not to let you rush things.
Get plenty of rest
so you can recover better.
I'm leaving.
Let's go fishing tomorrow.
We haven't fished in a long time.
And when Mentor comes back,
we can have spicy fish.
It's raining.
Will the rain stop tomorrow?
This terrible weather! I...
My good bait is completely wasted.
It wasn't easy to get this Shilixiang.
I was planning to catch a big fish.
The weather is bad.
There's nothing we can do.
I don't think so.
Maybe, with this weather,
the rain will stop in a while.
Let me feel it.
Young Masters!
Are you going out?
There...
We've had a typhoon these past few days,
and it'll probably last a few more days.
It's better not to go out.
-It's all wet.
-This weather is awful.
Could it be the heavenly ghost
making trouble in Xiacheng?
I heard that
when the heavenly ghost appears,
bad things will happen.
Really?
What year is this?
They still believe this nonsense?
Shrimpie,
let's do something else.
What should we do?
Now that I suddenly have some free time,
I don't know what to do.
How about playing chess?
That's boring.
Why don't we play something exciting?
Put me down!
Zhang Hailou, put me down!
I won't!
Sit tight, Shrimpie!
Stop!
Turn right!
Shrimpie,
the weather is finally fine.
Let's go sea fishing.
You call this fine weather?
I can't go.
Isn't the boat right there?
Just bring it over.
The sea is too rough.
We can't go out to sea.
I'll pay you more.
It's not about money.
Why can't we go?
The sea is too rough.
-I'll double it, okay?
-Still dreaming things can be like they used to be?
Why can't I make you understand?
These waves aren't dangerous at all.
You're just a burden now.
Figure it out yourself.
Why can't I reason with you?
If you want to go so badly,
find someone else to take you. Go.
Trash shouldn't be alive.
Like I care!
Don't hold me up.
I need to haul in the net and go home.
Stop fooling yourself.
[Excessive use of strychnine may lead to madness;
physicians should prescribe with utmost caution.]
[Long-term use
may lead to personality changes.]
What is wrong with me lately?
[Long-term use
may lead to personality changes.]
[Pharmacy]
Mr. Zhang,
there is nothing wrong with your health.
You can stay under observation
for a while.
Come to me if you have any problems.
[Award of Commendation]
Mimi,
come down!
Mimi, come down!
Come down.
Let me do it.
Can you?
Who told you
to throw the stone at the cat?
You almost killed it!
-Yuanbao!
-I...
Come down!
Are you okay?
What are you doing?
I was just trying to help.
Mother,
he threw a stone at Mimi!
I...
Stop it!
Doing such a despicable thing at your age!
Shameless!
Are you going to explain?
Will they believe you if you explain?
No one can even understand
your good intentions,
let alone believe anything else you say.
Zhang Hailou and your mentor are the same.
[No animals were hurt
during the shooting]
Give me the cat!
Let me go! You...
Let go! You're hurting me!
-Let go of my mother!
-Yuanbao! Come back! Yuanbao!
Let me go!
You're hurting me!
No!
Let go of my mother!
Give me the cat!
Let's go!
Let's go home! Hurry!
I...
Young Master,
you're awake? Breakfast is ready.
[Murder]
[Crossword Puzzle]
Young Master, the doctor is here.
He is waiting for you in the room.
Young Master?
What's the rush?
I'm coming.
Great. Yes.
Take a step. Come on.
Be careful.
Yes, very good.
Yes.
Come on.
A little more.
Yes.
Are you okay?
Steady.
Come on.
Good.
You can do it.
Yes, very good.
Come on.
Slow down.
Be careful. Steady.
Hold on.
Good. Keep your balance.
Come on.
You're doing great.
Good.
No rush.
You were being awesome today.
Let's stop here. I'll get you some water.
Run!
Slow down!
We're taking off!